In this section, we'll focus on tasks to evaluate inputs, which can be important for ensuring the quality and safety of the system.
在本节中，我们将重点关注评估输入的任务，这对于确保系统的质量和安全性非常重要。
For tasks in which lots of independent sets of instructions are needed to handle different cases,
对于需要处理不同情况的大量独立指令集的任务，
it can be beneficial to first classify the type of query and then use that classification to determine which instructions to use.
首先对查询类型进行分类，然后使用该分类来确定要使用哪些指令可能会有益。
This can be achieved by defining fixed categories and hard coding instructions that are relevant for handling tasks in a given category.
这可以通过定义固定类别和硬编码与处理给定类别任务相关的指令来实现。
For instance, when building a customer service assistant, it might be important to first classify the type of query and then determine which instructions to use based on that classification.
例如，在构建客户服务助手时，首先对查询类型进行分类，然后根据该分类确定要使用哪些指令可能非常重要。
So, for example, you might give different secondary instructions if a user asked to close their account versus if a user asked about a specific product.
因此，例如，如果用户要求关闭其帐户，您可能会提供不同的次要指令，而如果用户要求有关特定产品的信息，则可能会提供其他次要指令。
So in the first case, you maybe add additional instructions about how to close the account.
因此，在第一种情况下，您可能会添加有关如何关闭帐户的其他指令。
And then in the second case, you might add additional product instructions.
然后在第二种情况下，您可能会添加其他产品指令。
But let's see an example and I think it will make it more clear.
但是让我们看一个例子，我认为这会更清楚。
So here we have our system message, which is the instruction for the overall system.
所以这里我们有我们的系统消息，这是整个系统的指令。
And we're using this delimiter.
我们正在使用这个分隔符。
And it's limiter is just a way to separate different parts of an instruction or output.
它的限制器只是一种分隔指令或输出不同部分的方法。
And it helps the model kind of determine the different sections.
它有助于模型确定不同的部分。
And so for this example, we'll use the delimiter for hash tags.
因此，对于此示例，我们将使用哈希标签作为分隔符。
And this is a nice delimiter because it's actually represented as one token.
这是一个不错的分隔符，因为它实际上表示为一个标记。
And so here's our system message.
这是我们的系统消息。
What we're asking the model.
我们要求模型做什么。
So you will be provided with customer service queries.
您将获得客户服务查询。
The customer service query will be delimited with these hash tag characters.
客户服务查询将用这些哈希标记字符分隔。
Classify each query into a primary category and a secondary category and then provide the output in a JSON format with the keys primary and secondary.
将每个查询分类为主要类别和次要类别，然后以JSON格式提供输出，其中键为primary和secondary。
And so we have our primary categories listed here.
这里列出了我们的主要类别。
So billing, technical support, account management or general inquiry.
因此，计费、技术支持、帐户管理或一般查询。
And then below we have the list of secondary categories.
然后在下面，我们列出了次要类别的列表。
Unsubscriber upgrade, etc.
取消订阅升级等。
And so now let's do an example of a user message.
现在，让我们举一个用户消息的例子。
So for our first user message, we'll use.
因此，对于我们的第一个用户消息，我们将使用。
The following.
以下。
So the user messages, I want you to delete my profile and all of my user data.
因此，用户消息，我要求您删除我的个人资料和所有用户数据。
And then we'll just format this into a messages list with the system message and the user message delimited with these hash tags.
然后，我们将其格式化为消息列表，其中系统消息和用户消息用这些哈希标记分隔。
And let's just take a look and see what we think this might be.
让我们看看我们认为这可能是什么。
So I want you to delete my profile.
所以我要求您删除我的个人资料。
This kind of looks like account management.
这有点像帐户管理。
Maybe close account.
也许是关闭帐户。
So let's see what the model thinks.
让我们看看模型的想法。
Great.
很好。
So the classification from the model is account management as the primary category and then close account as a secondary.
因此，模型的分类是帐户管理作为主要类别，关闭帐户作为次要类别。
And the nice thing about asking for a structured output like a JSON is that you can then read this easily into some kind of object.
请求结构化输出（如JSON）的好处在于，您可以将其轻松地读入某种对象中。
So a dictionary, for example, in Python or something else if you're using a different language.
例如，在Python中使用字典，或者如果您使用不同的语言，则使用其他内容。
And then you can use this as the input to a subsequent step.
然后，您可以将此用作后续步骤的输入。
I'll show you another example, but also feel free to pause the video now and just try your own user questions and see how the model categorizes them.
我将向您展示另一个示例，但现在可以随时暂停视频并尝试自己的用户问题，看看模型如何对其进行分类。
So here's another user message.
这是另一个用户消息。
Tell me more about your flat screen TVs.
告诉我更多关于你的平板电视。
And we just have the same messages list response from the model and then we'll just print it.
然后我们只需从模型中获得相同的消息列表响应，然后将其打印出来。
And here we have our second categorization, which seems correct.
在这里，我们有第二个分类，看起来是正确的。
And so in general, based on the categorization of the customer inquiry, we can now provide a set of more specific instructions to handle the next steps.
因此，基于客户查询的分类，我们现在可以提供一组更具体的指令来处理下一步。
In this case, we might add kind of additional information about the TVs versus in this case, we might want to give a link to closing the account or something like that.
在这种情况下，我们可能会添加有关电视的其他信息，而在这种情况下，我们可能希望提供关闭帐户的链接或类似内容。
We'll learn more about different ways to process inputs in a later video.
我们将在以后的视频中了解有关处理输入的不同方法。
And in the next video, we'll look at more ways to evaluate inputs and specifically ways to ensure that your users are using the system in a responsible way.
在下一个视频中，我们将探讨更多评估输入的方法，特别是确保您的用户以负责任的方式使用系统的方法。